{"codeQuality":"Strengths: Uses TypeScript with proper config; Files are well-sized and modular; Good inline documentation; Has test files. Areas for improvement: No linting/formatting configuration found; No error handling patterns detected","readmeClarity":"Strengths: Comprehensive documentation; Well-structured with multiple sections; Installation instructions; Feature list included; Tech stack documented. Areas for improvement: Missing usage examples","projectStructure":"Strengths: Has dedicated src/ directory. Areas for improvement: All files in root directory ÔÇö consider organizing into folders; Missing .gitignore","innovation":"Strengths: Uses multiple languages; ML/AI integration; Rich dependency set (70 packages)","technical":"Strengths: Environment configuration; Modular file organization","summary":"Overall Score: 56/100. The submission demonstrates moderate technical capabilities.","aiRecommendation":"NEEDS_REVIEW","confidence":51,"reasoning":"Candidate shows potential but has areas requiring attention. Overall score: 56/100. KEY STRENGTHS: strong code quality (77/100). AI VERDICT: This candidate requires HR review. The submission shows potential but has significant gaps. Consider the specific role requirements before deciding."}
